Guide to the Caribbean and Latin American Postcard Collection
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Caribbean and Latin American postcard collection
1890-1984
MS 2020
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
0.5
(1 box)
This collection consists of postcards and photos from 1890 to 1920 from countries and territories in Latin America and the Caribbean, including Barbados, Bermuda, Cuba, Jamaica, Martinique, Puerto Rico, Panama, Trinidad and Tobago, Venezuela, and Madeira. It also includes a small number of postcards depicting Gibraltar, photographs of the building of the Panama Canal, and artistic postcards from Chile published in 1984.
Scope and Contents
This collection consists of postcards and photos from 1890 to 1920 from countries and territories in Latin America and the Caribbean, including Barbados, Bermuda, Cuba, Jamaica, Martinique, Puerto Rico, Panama, Trinidad and Tobago, Venezuela, and Madeira. It also includes a small number of postcards depicting Gibraltar, photographs of the building of the Panama Canal, and artistic postcards from Chile published in 1984.
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research.
Arrangement
The materials are arranged by country.
Postcards; Barbados; Bermuda Islands; Chile; Cuba; Gibraltar; Jamaica; Martinique; Panama Canal (Panama); Panama; Puerto Rico; Trinidad and Tobago; Venezuela
- Bridgetown, Barbados, Islands, 1900-1920; 13 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Bermuda Islands, Hamilton and Buildings, 1912-1920; 12 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Bermudia Islands, Views, 1910-1920; 10 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Cuba, Antilla, Nipe Bay, 1910-1920; 6 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Cuba, Bayamo, 1910-1920; 2 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Cuba, Camaguey, 1910-1920; 13 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Havana, Cuba, 1900-1920; 13 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Matanzas, Cuba, 1900-1920; 3 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Cuba, Miscellaneous, 1900-1920; 5 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Cuba, Santa Clara, 1900-1920; 1 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Santiago de Cuba, Buildings of City, 1900-1920; 8 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Santiago de Cuba,Views, 1900-1920; 11 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Cuba, Views, 1910-1920; 7 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Jamaica, 1900-1920; 2 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- St. Pierre, Martinique. Interior English Cathedral before destruction, 1902, 1900-1902; 1 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Fort-de-France, Martinique, Buildings, 1900-1920; 10 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Martinique Island, Fort-de-France, Views, 1900-1920; 11 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Ruins of St. Pierre, Martinique Island, 1900-1915; 3 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- San Juan, Puerto Rico, 1909-1912; 11 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Colon, Panama, 1900-1915; 1 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Panama City, 1900-1920; 10 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Porto Bello (Panama), 1900-1920; 1 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Culebra, Panama Canal, 1890-1913; 4 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Gatun, Panama Canal, 1906-1914; 8 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Gorgona, Panama Canal, 1904-1914; 1 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Miraflores, Panama Canal, 1909-1914; 3 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Panama Canal, giscellaneous, 1904-1914; 2 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Pedro Miguel, Panama Canal, 1904-1911; 2 (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Y.M.C.A. Buildings, Panama Canal Zone and Other Buildings, 1904-1914; 4 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Taboga Island, Panama, 1900-1915; 2 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Tobago, Trinidad and Tobago, 1900-1915; 1 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Trinidad, Port-of-Spain and La Brea, 1900-1920; 15 (Box 1, Folder 32)
- Venezuela, Caracas, Buildings, 1900-1920; 12 (Box 1, Folder 33)
- Venezuela, Caracas, Views, 1900-1920; 10 (Box 1, Folder 34)
- Venezuela, La Guaira, 1900-1920; 8 (Box 1, Folder 35)
- Gibraltar, City and Street Views, 1900-1920; 12 (Box 1, Folder 36)
- Gibraltar, Military Views, 1910-1920; 5 (Box 1, Folder 37)
- Gibraltar, The Rock of, 1900-1920; 7 (Box 1, Folder 38)
- Madeira, Funchal, 1912, 5 (Box 1, Folder 39)
- Santiago de Chile, Views, 1984, 24 (Box 1, Folder 40)